<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Disney Tips - bound.tips</title>
    <link>https://disney.bound.tips</link>
    <description>Daily Disney tips extracted from top YouTube channels</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:56:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>https://disney.bound.tips/og-image.png</url>
      <title>Disney Tips - bound.tips</title>
      <link>https://disney.bound.tips</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy Magic Kingdom Monorail resort hopping, starting at the Polynesian, Grand Floridian, and Con...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TBpZpWe8-xQ</link>
      <description>Enjoy Magic Kingdom Monorail resort hopping, starting at the Polynesian, Grand Floridian, and Contemporary Resorts. (Source: ResortTV1)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17c56d3e-0738-4938-9740-979d5a7ef8c5</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book hard-to-find restaurant reservations using the Dreamtable app.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TBpZpWe8-xQ</link>
      <description>Book hard-to-find restaurant reservations using the Dreamtable app. (Source: ResortTV1)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6060558b-6360-43c4-8782-94d885381cb2</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider a morning stream at Magic Kingdom for a different park experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TBpZpWe8-xQ</link>
      <description>Consider a morning stream at Magic Kingdom for a different park experience. (Source: ResortTV1)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">265ba231-68bf-4c24-b0f0-c563ba01393c</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book a DVC room through David&apos;s DVC Rentals for a fraction of the cost.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TBpZpWe8-xQ</link>
      <description>Book a DVC room through David&apos;s DVC Rentals for a fraction of the cost. (Source: ResortTV1)</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acc84bc5-31fa-4952-b2bd-4cc56c8b22ab</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab bubble wands from the Easter section at Walmart for around $8.98, which is cheaper than the ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Grab bubble wands from the Easter section at Walmart for around $8.98, which is cheaper than the toy section. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75686812-a124-4e6e-943d-c14acab5f413</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purchase glow wands for nighttime use in the parks; they are much brighter and last longer than g...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Purchase glow wands for nighttime use in the parks; they are much brighter and last longer than glow sticks. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e34c13d-e3c6-4626-8a8b-6eb599136e40</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider buying shoe rain jackets to keep your footwear dry if you anticipate getting caught in t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Consider buying shoe rain jackets to keep your footwear dry if you anticipate getting caught in the rain, especially for water rides. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0122570b-f322-4cf2-8224-22aa8508056d</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run, don&apos;t walk, to get the Winnie the Pooh Christmas bag from the Disney Store if you plan a Chr...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Run, don&apos;t walk, to get the Winnie the Pooh Christmas bag from the Disney Store if you plan a Christmas trip, as they sell out quickly. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cf1f82c-9a0d-4a59-8ff0-d4d4139e08d5</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use the save for later feature on Amazon to monitor items and purchase them when they go on sale.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Use the save for later feature on Amazon to monitor items and purchase them when they go on sale. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3ba96cf-414f-4bbb-afa9-e0a78179cd24</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider bringing the comfortable, oversized t-shirt and bike short sets for travel days or as a ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Consider bringing the comfortable, oversized t-shirt and bike short sets for travel days or as a comfy backup outfit. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57080a5a-65eb-4a7b-ae7d-253ff68731e8</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider using shoe rain jackets for water rides like Kali River Rapids to protect your footwear.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Consider using shoe rain jackets for water rides like Kali River Rapids to protect your footwear. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83499e7d-6a10-407f-a191-e23bf61a0e88</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invest in the vitamin spray for daily use, especially during flu season, as it can help prevent i...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2T1bdK2HIsw</link>
      <description>Invest in the vitamin spray for daily use, especially during flu season, as it can help prevent illness during your trip. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8536bfbd-6513-4f62-aae4-4e26a2df4bd6</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy the Dapper Dans performing on Main Street, U.S.A. for a classic Magic Kingdom experience.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e0LDIV7nr_E</link>
      <description>Enjoy the Dapper Dans performing on Main Street, U.S.A. for a classic Magic Kingdom experience. (Source: ResortTV1)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:01:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb0b427b-089d-4cf0-94aa-afda4659b5e5</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you have a dining reservation in a different park or resort, start traveling to your destinati...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>If you have a dining reservation in a different park or resort, start traveling to your destination 1-2 hours before your reservation to avoid being late. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38e995db-bb60-4b5b-97f8-39395d1fd152</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider sharing large quick-service entrees, especially those that come with multiple items or a...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Consider sharing large quick-service entrees, especially those that come with multiple items or are listed as platters, to save money and reduce food waste. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e734939a-464e-438a-92a6-b5247ce9cbcf</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order children&apos;s meals at quick-service locations for a more affordable and smaller portioned opt...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Order children&apos;s meals at quick-service locations for a more affordable and smaller portioned option, which adults can also order. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">329c1785-4c30-4c19-b57b-4cca029c2c68</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip sodas at quick-service locations and opt for free water to save money and avoid feeling full...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Skip sodas at quick-service locations and opt for free water to save money and avoid feeling full before your meal. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">996e923f-9bb9-4e6a-a3e5-af887eca15af</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inquire at quick-service locations like Pinocchio Village House or select Columbia Harbor House i...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Inquire at quick-service locations like Pinocchio Village House or select Columbia Harbor House items if you can order without a side to save approximately $2. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dddc648-727f-44a0-87ed-0d7f1402dd27</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Always ask about available discounts for Annual Passholders, Disney Visa cardholders, or other me...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Always ask about available discounts for Annual Passholders, Disney Visa cardholders, or other membership groups at dining locations and merchandise spots, as they are not always proactively offered. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc013297-9016-41a0-9ca6-b621118c0c14</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When dining at a character restaurant with a buffet, watch the characters&apos; locations in the dinin...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>When dining at a character restaurant with a buffet, watch the characters&apos; locations in the dining room and delay your buffet trip to avoid missing an interaction at your table. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34f4200a-50f3-435a-a79e-3e83aba37cce</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book character dining experiences for breakfast as it is typically the cheapest option and still ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Book character dining experiences for breakfast as it is typically the cheapest option and still offers opportunities for hugs and pictures. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b8fac45-7c12-42d9-8975-7591f49c5364</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take advantage of happy hour deals at Disney Springs restaurants, which can offer savings on food...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Take advantage of happy hour deals at Disney Springs restaurants, which can offer savings on food, drinks, and sometimes even full entrees. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fcc8743-2ec8-44d9-b79d-fa1da5f2eb44</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>Disney Springs</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order popular off-menu items like &apos;Ohana noodles and bread pudding from Tambu Lounge at Polynesia...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Order popular off-menu items like &apos;Ohana noodles and bread pudding from Tambu Lounge at Polynesian Village to save money compared to a full Ohana meal. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5937d8-a829-404a-af19-215205739c64</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book the Space 220 lounge or try for walk-up bar availability in Epcot to order &apos;flight bites&apos; at...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Book the Space 220 lounge or try for walk-up bar availability in Epcot to order &apos;flight bites&apos; at individual prices instead of the full prix fixe meal cost. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92b29a00-46e9-4571-a238-a55bc384cf39</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>EPCOT</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the Smoky Mushroom Bisque or barbecue pork ribs, which are also available off-menu at Territo...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Get the Smoky Mushroom Bisque or barbecue pork ribs, which are also available off-menu at Territory Lounge at Wilderness Lodge, for a lower price than at Artist Point or Whispering Canyon. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebff36a9-1184-4cf9-a120-84b7bac2cd93</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure a walk-up spot at the California Grill bar in the Contemporary Resort to order a la carte ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>Secure a walk-up spot at the California Grill bar in the Contemporary Resort to order a la carte bites and still access the outdoor balcony for fireworks views at a lower cost than dinner. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de076d3e-d3ea-4ff1-956b-97c246e1001e</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To maximize the Disney Dining Plan, prioritize booking pricier table-service locations like buffe...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_R4BaIW20Rc</link>
      <description>To maximize the Disney Dining Plan, prioritize booking pricier table-service locations like buffets, family-style meals, or multi-course experiences to get the most value from your credits. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9221c017-8bef-4bff-be63-dbdc59ed5b8d</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When booking a Disney World hotel, avoid rooms facing the pools or those near the lobby as they t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>When booking a Disney World hotel, avoid rooms facing the pools or those near the lobby as they tend to be the loudest. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6303b5da-205c-4f9f-898f-a37b997bd133</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opt for rooms away from transportation hubs like bus stops or monorail stations to minimize noise...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>Opt for rooms away from transportation hubs like bus stops or monorail stations to minimize noise at your resort. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8740667-90cb-4f82-a994-11f0314b33a7</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To find quieter rooms at All-Star Resorts, request a courtyard or parking lot view and ask to be ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>To find quieter rooms at All-Star Resorts, request a courtyard or parking lot view and ask to be in a section far from the main pool or lobby, like the Love Bug or Mighty Ducks areas at All-Star Movies. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0590ef8d-e61a-4e1e-99b4-d0d998342d9b</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Pop Century Resort, avoid preferred or standard pool view rooms; instead, request a courtyard ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>At Pop Century Resort, avoid preferred or standard pool view rooms; instead, request a courtyard or landscaping view, or ask for a room in the &apos;90s section which is farthest from the main pool. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18312a7b-25a2-4d0a-bc6f-d5687971db3e</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request a room on a higher floor at the Contemporary Resort to reduce noise from the Monorail and...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>Request a room on a higher floor at the Contemporary Resort to reduce noise from the Monorail and dining areas. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d3cc563-9557-4509-9e07-78e8d74a8f01</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For a quieter stay at the Contemporary Resort, consider booking a room at Bay Lake Tower, which i...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>For a quieter stay at the Contemporary Resort, consider booking a room at Bay Lake Tower, which is adjacent to the main building. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b96fc30-cf25-413d-a396-e3c88b9fad24</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request an upper floor room when checking in to minimize noise from the Monorail and dining areas...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>Request an upper floor room when checking in to minimize noise from the Monorail and dining areas at the Contemporary Resort. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa1ae429-cd0b-4829-93e6-5a54debac9e9</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When requesting a room, ask to be located away from pools, elevators, and transportation hubs to ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>When requesting a room, ask to be located away from pools, elevators, and transportation hubs to ensure a quieter experience. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30f5babe-1ab2-4388-8d91-3b9422fc6462</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid rooms with exterior hallways whenever possible, as they tend to be noisier.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>Avoid rooms with exterior hallways whenever possible, as they tend to be noisier. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce8e7e11-66a0-4cf6-85cd-019273b12297</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check in at the front desk in person and be friendly with the Cast Member; they are more likely t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I3yOCZo-M20</link>
      <description>Check in at the front desk in person and be friendly with the Cast Member; they are more likely to accommodate your room requests when given face-to-face. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9845918e-66cc-4952-8280-7a78285eede6</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try the rotational dining on the Disney Treasure, as it is considered the best among the Disney c...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T6cVxc7ztbs</link>
      <description>Try the rotational dining on the Disney Treasure, as it is considered the best among the Disney cruise ships. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:00:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c33be6-65b2-413b-864f-153a43c65e3a</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To avoid long waits, head to the ship&apos;s rides right when they open or during port days when most ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>To avoid long waits, head to the ship&apos;s rides right when they open or during port days when most guests are ashore. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ba3f97-6eb3-4c59-bce9-f3c096ceef54</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check the wattage and voltage of your hair dryer before your cruise to ensure it meets Disney&apos;s s...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Check the wattage and voltage of your hair dryer before your cruise to ensure it meets Disney&apos;s safety requirements (1500W max for 110V or 2000W max for 220V) and avoid confiscation. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8316a34-8f51-462b-96af-297eef77edc6</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Disney cruises during shoulder seasons like fall for the Bahamas/Caribbean (outside hurrican...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Book Disney cruises during shoulder seasons like fall for the Bahamas/Caribbean (outside hurricane season) or September for better prices and milder temperatures. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afc0d7b3-84f9-42fe-88f0-178a4a510674</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On cruises of seven nights or longer, take advantage of the formal and semi-formal nights to dres...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>On cruises of seven nights or longer, take advantage of the formal and semi-formal nights to dress up and utilize the ship&apos;s photography services. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd42a25e-c2a1-44d2-87ee-1d6c4485b0fd</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To avoid roaming fees, download movies, shows, books, and offline games onto your devices before ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>To avoid roaming fees, download movies, shows, books, and offline games onto your devices before boarding the ship. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3911e785-6295-4f1b-8eaa-31f0a60056f5</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the best view of shows and fireworks on the cruise deck&apos;s main stage, find a spot on Deck 12 ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>For the best view of shows and fireworks on the cruise deck&apos;s main stage, find a spot on Deck 12 instead of trying to get close to the stage. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eed5c985-3163-4807-956a-91d7ba60568f</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take advantage of free onboard activities like karaoke, sketch classes, napkin folding, and trivi...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Take advantage of free onboard activities like karaoke, sketch classes, napkin folding, and trivia games instead of paying for extra entertainment. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41389a91-733b-4c1b-a572-056ac5708468</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepay gratuities for your dining room server, assistant server, head server, and stateroom host ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Prepay gratuities for your dining room server, assistant server, head server, and stateroom host on the DCL website or Navigator app under &apos;My Reservations&apos; to handle tips in advance. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">594b23f8-43ec-44df-a0bb-3efbb8dd0d43</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book a cruise during Pixar Day at Sea or Marvel Day at Sea for themed entertainment, dining, and ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Book a cruise during Pixar Day at Sea or Marvel Day at Sea for themed entertainment, dining, and character meet-and-greets. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427b4f9e-8809-4f30-b545-bce0b6328ab1</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience Halloween on the High Seas with a cruise-long celebration including costumed character...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Experience Halloween on the High Seas with a cruise-long celebration including costumed characters, a parade, crafts, and trick-or-treating. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81dcd2f-f9f6-4744-b9d4-56db5305eeee</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book a cruise during the Very Merry Time Cruises for a ship-wide holiday celebration with a tree ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Book a cruise during the Very Merry Time Cruises for a ship-wide holiday celebration with a tree lighting, parties, crafts, and visits from Santa Claus. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b01210db-ac52-4c78-99d8-615a26e09803</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy a special New Year&apos;s dinner and an exclusive fireworks display if you are cruising on New Y...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rTkwNhyPVO8</link>
      <description>Enjoy a special New Year&apos;s dinner and an exclusive fireworks display if you are cruising on New Year&apos;s Eve. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a741b1b3-721a-430f-9633-c449b57b9af2</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
