<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Disney Tips - bound.tips</title>
    <link>https://disney.bound.tips</link>
    <description>Daily Disney tips extracted from top YouTube channels</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:23:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>1440</ttl>
    <image>
      <url>https://disney.bound.tips/og-image.png</url>
      <title>Disney Tips - bound.tips</title>
      <link>https://disney.bound.tips</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid talking too loudly about behind-the-scenes facts within earshot of other guests, especially...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iKx_9rtFks</link>
      <description>Avoid talking too loudly about behind-the-scenes facts within earshot of other guests, especially children, to maintain the magic for them. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eca658d6-bb7d-4fab-a729-79ffe1e7059d</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not force children onto rides if they seem apprehensive, as their perception of scariness diff...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iKx_9rtFks</link>
      <description>Do not force children onto rides if they seem apprehensive, as their perception of scariness differs from adults&apos;. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dbea83c-418b-44e5-9d23-20ae7be52fe4</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not use flash photos or videos on dark rides, as this violates an official rule and can ruin t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9iKx_9rtFks</link>
      <description>Do not use flash photos or videos on dark rides, as this violates an official rule and can ruin the ride&apos;s effects and illusion for others. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b35ba093-6d86-402b-9433-56ad2faffc0d</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab the Wilderness Explorers activity book near the park entrance to engage children in learning...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Grab the Wilderness Explorers activity book near the park entrance to engage children in learning about the park&apos;s animals and plants. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a7e1d61-187e-463b-888d-8d2d5d93231d</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile order breakfast at Satu&apos;li Canteen before 10:00 a.m. to ensure you can get your desired meal.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Mobile order breakfast at Satu&apos;li Canteen before 10:00 a.m. to ensure you can get your desired meal. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c8fb2a0-9b7b-45e9-a7b2-18cd3228f434</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask a Cast Member at Satu&apos;li Canteen for to-go boxes to transfer your mobile order food into, and...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Ask a Cast Member at Satu&apos;li Canteen for to-go boxes to transfer your mobile order food into, and then get your plastic ware from a nearby quick-service spot. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">794bb62f-ad30-4ac8-9a66-588e10661342</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consider purchasing a single rider pass for Expedition Everest to save time, as it significantly ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Consider purchasing a single rider pass for Expedition Everest to save time, as it significantly reduces wait times. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bbb83df-4ee3-48c6-894e-5ef43c3a0eaf</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If visiting Animal Kingdom during the &apos;slow season&apos; without early entry, consider purchasing a si...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>If visiting Animal Kingdom during the &apos;slow season&apos; without early entry, consider purchasing a single Lightning Lane pass for popular rides like Flight of Passage to save time. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab379e69-9c32-4fc8-8a34-9efeb9d54f5b</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Frozen Lemonade Cappuccino at Pomatoka is an extra delicious beverage to enjoy while in Anima...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>The Frozen Lemonade Cappuccino at Pomatoka is an extra delicious beverage to enjoy while in Animal Kingdom. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0ccb285-a048-4118-81d6-875cda3346ed</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dinoland U.S.A. in Animal Kingdom is permanently closing and will not be available for visits.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Dinoland U.S.A. in Animal Kingdom is permanently closing and will not be available for visits. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ffb8e9d-1a24-4d91-a421-33c3f035c1af</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If the weather is cool and breezy, consider skipping Kali River Rapids, as it may be too cold to ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>If the weather is cool and breezy, consider skipping Kali River Rapids, as it may be too cold to enjoy getting wet. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebda2571-e609-423c-bcfd-91150f46ad02</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal Kingdom remains worth visiting in 2026, even with ongoing construction, as key areas like ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>Animal Kingdom remains worth visiting in 2026, even with ongoing construction, as key areas like Pandora and Africa offer a full experience. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16d23383-73a7-458c-ab0a-fe75fc962bb0</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During slower seasons, it&apos;s possible to enjoy Animal Kingdom and ride most attractions without pu...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qpw-f0qRXj0</link>
      <description>During slower seasons, it&apos;s possible to enjoy Animal Kingdom and ride most attractions without purchasing many Lightning Lanes, especially if utilizing early entry. (Source: PixieDustedMom)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbfab05c-71e7-4b21-b89a-73273bbfb4ef</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To see backstage areas, book official Disney tours like Keys to the Kingdom at Magic Kingdom or W...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>To see backstage areas, book official Disney tours like Keys to the Kingdom at Magic Kingdom or Wild Africa Trek at Animal Kingdom. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff2ed8eb-d580-487b-a11c-c260e8c657fa</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research ride height requirements before your trip to avoid disappointment and ensure your childr...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Research ride height requirements before your trip to avoid disappointment and ensure your children can ride. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3449e95f-3ab4-4c79-a94b-522d11c8d366</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilize Rider Switch for any group member who cannot or does not want to ride an attraction, so t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Utilize Rider Switch for any group member who cannot or does not want to ride an attraction, so they don&apos;t have to wait alone. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d68cea8e-1015-4521-a6e6-1e80a93cc684</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When attending special events like parties or extended evening hours, wear your required wristban...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>When attending special events like parties or extended evening hours, wear your required wristband visibly to avoid being escorted from the park. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6941e5e9-facd-4e8d-b4f0-5aa836d18b06</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refrain from reciting ride pre-show dialogue out loud, even if you know it by heart, to avoid ann...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Refrain from reciting ride pre-show dialogue out loud, even if you know it by heart, to avoid annoyance for other guests. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20b01363-9c91-4653-8c59-37a4932ace35</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not feed the wildlife in the parks, as it is against Disney rules and harmful to the animals&apos; ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not feed the wildlife in the parks, as it is against Disney rules and harmful to the animals&apos; health and behavior. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a486a964-318c-4f02-abd0-dc338b578841</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask cast members for directions or help with Lightning Lane selections, as they are trained and e...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Ask cast members for directions or help with Lightning Lane selections, as they are trained and eager to assist. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bac692ee-ce88-4139-982e-8fd3f4c3db9f</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engage with Epcot&apos;s cultural representatives to learn about their home countries, including dinin...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Engage with Epcot&apos;s cultural representatives to learn about their home countries, including dining recommendations and local customs. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54709c71-35b7-4fec-b503-f89a29aa90bf</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>EPCOT</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancel dining reservations at least two hours in advance via the My Disney Experience app or by c...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Cancel dining reservations at least two hours in advance via the My Disney Experience app or by calling to avoid a $10 per person no-show fee. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b5c5961-9424-4008-a687-5b10e1765f0e</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designated smoking areas are now located outside the parks; check the My Disney Experience app&apos;s ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Designated smoking areas are now located outside the parks; check the My Disney Experience app&apos;s guest services filter for locations. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d97d8afb-41bb-4f78-9476-66746cd4a5ff</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stay within designated taped-off areas during parades and fireworks to keep walkways clear for tr...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Stay within designated taped-off areas during parades and fireworks to keep walkways clear for traffic and emergency access. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91dcca4a-7cc5-46ea-b5e0-c99ad6b9dc4c</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you need over-the-counter medication while at your resort, check the gift shop, though prices ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>If you need over-the-counter medication while at your resort, check the gift shop, though prices will be slightly elevated. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79dee2e5-030e-4de4-8e12-444cf2825b83</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not walk barefoot in public Disney spaces like buses or hotel lobbies; save that for your hote...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not walk barefoot in public Disney spaces like buses or hotel lobbies; save that for your hotel room. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fa8d587-62ae-4ff6-82a0-4ad2f2649734</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When checking in for a table-service meal, you can request a specific table (e.g., with a firewor...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>When checking in for a table-service meal, you can request a specific table (e.g., with a fireworks view), but it is not guaranteed. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcbf441e-9129-4bea-ac2b-83057cedf46d</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For guaranteed fireworks views, book dining at restaurants like California Grill at the Contempor...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>For guaranteed fireworks views, book dining at restaurants like California Grill at the Contemporary Resort, which has a dedicated viewing area. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4df5e8f5-3f88-4322-9792-18ce8c140da5</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have your food and payment ready before reaching the register at Epcot festival booths and quick-...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Have your food and payment ready before reaching the register at Epcot festival booths and quick-service locations to expedite your order. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f0e3410-6a93-4c94-a01d-7f47250cda72</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not bring outside alcohol, foods in glass containers (except baby food), foods requiring heati...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not bring outside alcohol, foods in glass containers (except baby food), foods requiring heating/refrigeration, or pungent foods into the parks. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfe741dd-e0ab-4942-8d88-ac4253be2f6a</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To skip attraction queues, utilize the Lightning Lane service or the single rider option where av...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>To skip attraction queues, utilize the Lightning Lane service or the single rider option where available. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01e9d3f1-6e50-4cfc-b366-216f1aadded6</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limit yourself to two alcoholic beverages per transaction at quick-service locations and Epcot fe...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Limit yourself to two alcoholic beverages per transaction at quick-service locations and Epcot festival booths to encourage responsible consumption. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30dc8599-a39f-4834-a534-4b622cb2ae75</guid>
      <category>Budget</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not save seats at quick-service restaurants if you do not have your food yet; wait until you h...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not save seats at quick-service restaurants if you do not have your food yet; wait until you have your tray to claim a table. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc0fe399-5d71-4ce5-8373-43f6e847c097</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refrain from using flash photography on rides, as it can ruin other guests&apos; experiences, affect p...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Refrain from using flash photography on rides, as it can ruin other guests&apos; experiences, affect performers, and potentially damage attractions; use the PhotoPass system instead. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41185736-72c7-47d5-b6f6-61c1c15a54ec</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep all body parts inside the ride vehicle at all times and avoid attempting to stand up or drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Keep all body parts inside the ride vehicle at all times and avoid attempting to stand up or drop items onto the track to prevent ride stoppages and ensure safety. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c8c5efd-746e-4000-955a-20d2187ede64</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Always ask permission before attempting to trade pins with a cast member, and adhere to the limit...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Always ask permission before attempting to trade pins with a cast member, and adhere to the limit of two trades per person per cast member. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a19a544-7448-4a6e-9b16-3fd91de26490</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send cast compliments via the My Disney Experience app for cast members who go above and beyond, ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Send cast compliments via the My Disney Experience app for cast members who go above and beyond, potentially allowing them to name a food cart. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a8a8a19-a0fe-4d69-becc-e2a40f726164</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Always ask permission before petting a service animal, even if they have a cast member name tag, ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Always ask permission before petting a service animal, even if they have a cast member name tag, as they are still working. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0aa1bf97-74ff-477e-a6d7-cbc3c29a0698</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not use trash can lids or other inappropriate surfaces as temporary seating for children due t...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not use trash can lids or other inappropriate surfaces as temporary seating for children due to safety hazards. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03df5f2a-aed8-489d-9e11-d5afcd3de5de</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not directly ask cast members for magical moments or freebies, as these require leader approva...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Do not directly ask cast members for magical moments or freebies, as these require leader approval and may not always be permissible. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd01b95d-7dee-413f-b38c-50474d4ed2c5</guid>
      <category>Planning</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid misusing hotel room appliances like irons for cooking; instead, pack non-perishable food it...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>Avoid misusing hotel room appliances like irons for cooking; instead, pack non-perishable food items or opt for rooms with kitchenettes. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f78ce2a-ca7e-4fb8-8da5-c82424832af7</guid>
      <category>Hotels</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For restaurants that encourage movement, consider Chef Mickey&apos;s (napkin twirling), Biergarten (da...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SXBjVVeprs</link>
      <description>For restaurants that encourage movement, consider Chef Mickey&apos;s (napkin twirling), Biergarten (dance floor), or &apos;Ohana (character parades) to keep children entertained during meals. (Source: DFBGuide)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da1ba76d-96a1-449c-8351-a5ab797de5ec</guid>
      <category>Dining</category>
      <category>All Parks</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the Voices of Liberty, an a capella group in the American Adventure Pavilion at Epcot, for an...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>See the Voices of Liberty, an a capella group in the American Adventure Pavilion at Epcot, for an amazing performance of Americana songs. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2964fe97-736a-47f5-af8f-cd6e80b0f731</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>EPCOT</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the new Disney Villains: Unfairly Ever After show in the Sunset Showcase at Hollywood Studi...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Watch the new Disney Villains: Unfairly Ever After show in the Sunset Showcase at Hollywood Studios; the audience reaction can lead to different endings. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0dd46e0-aa3d-4637-bdb7-b8405d4eea76</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Hollywood Studios</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Olaf in the Echo Lake area of Hollywood Studios, near the Vacation Fun Mickey short.</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Meet Olaf in the Echo Lake area of Hollywood Studios, near the Vacation Fun Mickey short. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c8055a9-ea5e-49e2-8312-6ec1b1d48fcd</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Hollywood Studios</category>
      <category>Low</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ride The Twilight Zone Tower of Terror at Hollywood Studios for its perfect blend of theming, sto...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Ride The Twilight Zone Tower of Terror at Hollywood Studios for its perfect blend of theming, storytelling, and thrill. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebd8aabe-9c3f-4f42-b199-34ded56db484</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Hollywood Studios</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enjoy a relaxing ride on the Tomorrowland Transit Authority PeopleMover in Magic Kingdom, especia...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Enjoy a relaxing ride on the Tomorrowland Transit Authority PeopleMover in Magic Kingdom, especially during the Happily Ever After fireworks for added magic. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036775db-0475-4f42-b75d-e529a4d9761b</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ride Rock &apos;n&apos; Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith at Hollywood Studios before it&apos;s re-themed to The...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Ride Rock &apos;n&apos; Roller Coaster Starring Aerosmith at Hollywood Studios before it&apos;s re-themed to The Muppets to experience the only attraction in Disney World that goes upside down. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f2b3847-1d8b-4d72-aa9b-4181aaa24515</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Hollywood Studios</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience the Haunted Mansion in Magic Kingdom&apos;s Liberty Square, a fun and hokey dark ride suita...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Experience the Haunted Mansion in Magic Kingdom&apos;s Liberty Square, a fun and hokey dark ride suitable for all ages. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cddfedeb-9a4f-40ff-a6a5-63c4b45caafc</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Magic Kingdom</category>
      <category>Medium</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ride Kilmanjaro Safaris in Animal Kingdom for a realistic safari experience with live animals on ...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cYFtkUAnJ2U</link>
      <description>Ride Kilmanjaro Safaris in Animal Kingdom for a realistic safari experience with live animals on a vast savannah. (Source: AllEars.net)</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7946a9cd-7677-4e03-966b-d84f22419430</guid>
      <category>Parks</category>
      <category>Animal Kingdom</category>
      <category>High</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
